Idan Joshua Garay

Junior Software Engineer

A highly motivated software engineer with a strong desire to advance to the role of principal software engineer, I am dedicated to continuous learning to further refine my skills and expertise in the field. A quick learner with a solid foundation in programming principles and techniques.

Professional Experience

Sports Social Platform, October 2022 - December 2022

Koda Kollectiv

- Learned the specific state management
- Created web components e.g. searchbar with users dropdown, and avatars for selected users.

Koda Kollectiv

Ticketing System, October 2022 - October 2022

- Tasked with creating web components for displaying backend data using Bootstrap
- Handled logic of back-end data
- Automated data generation for the MySQL backend using seeders.
- Modified database tables to meet the hidden data requirements, and relationship sidentified from the front-end.

Crisis Monitoring System, August 2022 - October 2022

Koda Kollectiv

- Developed front-end components e.g. collapsible sidebar, tabs
- Created web components e.g. searchbar with users dropdown, and avatars for selected users.

Static Websites August 2022 - December 2022

Koda Kollectiv

• Tasked with shaping websites to meet the clients' requirements while ensuring responsiveness.

Education

- **University of San Carlos** 2019 - Current (College)
- University of Cebu Banilad 2017 - 2019 (Senior Highschool)
- Saint Louis College Cebu 2013 - 2017 (Junior Highschool)

Expertise

- + React, Vue
- + Flutter (BLoC Pattern)
- + Javascript
- + Git Repositories
- + Typescript
- + Postman

- + HTML/CSS Fundamentals

Skills

- + Interpersonal Communication
- + Problem Solving
- + Leader
- + Teamwork
- + Attentive
- + Adaptability

Certifications

+ Shopee Code League 2022 - Participant

Contact Info



(+63) 993 783 6470



garayidan@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/idanjoshua-garay-1a4657176/